https://www.hyperoffice.com/terms-of-use/

Press enter to begin your search
Terms of UsePrivacy PolicyCookies PolicyHyperOffice Terms of UseLast Modified: March 15, 2019Thank you for choosing HyperOffice, provided to you by Application Corporation (d/b/a “HyperOffice”). These terms of service (the “Terms”) govern your access to and use of the HyperOffice services, including but not limited to HyperOffice Atlas, WorkMap.ai, HyperBase, uShare.to, and Share.to (the “Services”), so please carefully read them before using them.By registering an account to use the Services or by logging into the Service or by using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms . If you are using the Services on behalf of an organization, you are agreeing to these Terms for that organization and promising that you have the authority to bind that organization to these terms. In that case, “you” and “your” will refer to you and that organization. “We” or “our” will refer to HyperOffice.You may use the Services only in compliance with these Terms. You may use the Services only if you have the power to form a contract with HyperOffice. The Services may continue to change over time as we refine and add or remove features. We may stop, suspend, or modify the Services at any time without prior notice to you.Account Setup and AdministrationYour Account. When you register a new Account, an Account is set up for you corresponding to the Account Type you specified (e.g., Free Trial or Regular Account), the Subscription Period, the number of Registered Users under your Account and other feature selections. You agree not to set up duplicative Free Trial Accounts to circumvent the usage restrictions. When you register an Account, you represent that you are at least 13 years old and that, to the best of your knowledge and belief, your registration information is truthful, accurate and complete.Your Password. A username and password will be assigned by us or chosen by you. You will only access and use the Services through your own Account and only during the Subscription Period. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and for activities occurring under your Account (and each Registered User associated with your Account). Be sure to change your password promptly and notify us if you believe your Account has been compromised or is being accessed by others. Users may not loan their Accounts or passwords to others.Right to Rely on Instructions. The Service may act in reliance upon any instruction, information, document, filing, name, email address or user password that meets the Service’s automated criteria or which is believed by the Service’s personnel to be genuine. For any password protected areas, the Service may assume a person entering a user name address and associated password is, in fact, that user or is authorized by that user to act on its behalf. The Service may assume the latest email addresses and registration information on file with the Service are accurate and current. When programmed to do so, the Service may take prescribed actions in the absence of receiving proper and complete contrary instructions.Prices and PaymentSome features of the Service are available for a limited Free Trial period. If you use the Services beyond the Free Trial period, applicable charges will apply. Except for the limited Free Trial features, use of our Service requires the payment of charges, which may include one-time charges and recurring subscription-based fees or other charges that may be posted. We require timely payment of all published fees and charges by the Account holder at the time Services are ordered or as otherwise posted. Prices do not include, and you agree to pay, indemnify and hold HyperOffice harmless from all sales/use, gross receipts, value-added, GST, personal property or other tax (including interest and penalties thereon) on the transaction contemplated herein, other than taxes based on the net income or profits of HyperOffice.If you fail to pay applicable fees or charges when due, we may suspend or terminate your Account and the Services. Unless otherwise agreed in writing, all charges are payable in U.S. Dollars in advance by major credit card or other payment method specified in the registration page. Late payments are subject to costs of collection (including legal fees of 17.5% pre-filing, or 35% if formal legal proceedings are filed) and shall bear interest at a rate equal to the lesser of one (1) percent per month or the highest rate permitted by law.When you register an Account for a specified Subscription Period, the price may include a discount corresponding to the length of your commitment and specific selected features. We use these customer commitments collectively to obtain and schedule computing resources and staff to run the Service. Therefore, it is expressly agreed that Subscription Fees for the specified Subscription Period selected by you are non-refundable should you choose to cancel your Account prior to completion of the remaining Subscription Period for which you registered. Cancellation of the Account for payment purposes will become effective immediately prior to the next Subscription Period renewal date.If the Service is not accessible at least 99.9% of the time (as determined by the Service) for a continuous thirty (30) day period, then you may in the Service’s discretion and as your exclusive remedy be given pro-rata credit (1/30 th per day) of the monthly fee corresponding to that period, provided that you notify HyperOffice within seventy-two (72) hours of your inability to use the Service.If you received the Services through a Reseller Agreement, we reserve the right to condition access to the Services on our receipt of proper payment from the Reseller or, at our written request, from you directly.Your Content & Your PrivacyBy using our Services, you provide us with information, files and/or information, and folders that you submit to HyperOffice (collectively, your “Content”). You retain full exclusive ownership to your Content. We don’t claim any ownership to it. These Terms do not grant us any rights to your Content or intellectual property except for the limited rights that are needed to run the Services, as explained below.We may need your permission to do things you ask us to do with your Content, for example, hosting your files and/or information, or sharing them at your direction. This includes product features visible to you. It also includes design choices we make to technically administer our Services, for example, how we backup data to keep it safe. You give us the permissions we need to do those things solely to operate and administer the Services. Except for rare exceptions we identify in our Privacy Policy no matter how the Services change, we won’t share your content with others for any purpose unless you direct us to. How we collect and use your information generally is also explained in our Privacy Policy, incorporated herein by reference.You are solely responsible for your conduct, the Content you upload or store on the Services, and your communications with others while using the Services. For example, it’s your responsibility to ensure that you have the rights or permission needed to comply with these Terms.We may choose to review public content for compliance with our community guidelines, but you acknowledge that HyperOffice has no obligation to monitor any information on the Services. We are not responsible for the accuracy, completeness, appropriateness, or legality of files and/or information, user posts, or any other information you may be able to access or distribute using the Services.Sharing Your ContentThe Services provide features that allow you to share your Content with others or to make it public. There are many things that users may do with that Content (for example, copy it, modify it, re-share it). Please consider carefully what you choose to share or make public. HyperOffice has no responsibility for that activity.Your ResponsibilitiesFiles and/or information and other Content in the Services may be protected by intellectual property rights of you and others. Please do not copy, upload, download, or share files and/or information unless you have the right to do so. You, not HyperOffice, will be fully responsible and liable for what you copy, share, upload, download or otherwise use while using the Services. You must not upload spy-ware or any other malicious software to the Service.You, and not HyperOffice, are responsible for maintaining and protecting all of your Content. HyperOffice will not be liable for any loss or corruption of your Content, or for any costs or expenses associated with backing up or restoring any of your Content.If your contact information or other information related to your account, changes, you must notify us promptly and keep your information current. The Services are for business use and are not intended for use by you if you are under 13 years of age. By agreeing to these Terms, you are representing to us that you are over 13.Data RetentionWe retain the information we receive for as long as you use the Services or as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, provide our Services, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, enforce our agreements, and comply with applicable laws.Account SecurityYou are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access the Services and you agree not to disclose your password to any third party. You are responsible for any activity using your account, whether or not you authorized that activity. HyperOffice may rely on electronic instructions received through features of the Services through your account in carrying out those instructions. You should immediately notify HyperOffice of any unauthorized use of your account. You acknowledge that if you wish to protect your transmission of data or files and/or information to HyperOffice, it is your responsibility to use a secure encrypted connection to communicate with the Services.Data Management & DisclosureWe reserve the right to manage and operate our system resources and to archive any files and/or information stored on our Service at any time. You (the customer) are solely responsible for making back-up copies of any Customer Data or files and/or information that you wish to preserve. We may archive information and or delete information stored in accounts that are deemed “not in good standing” with our company. HyperOffice will take all reasonable steps to ensure all data archived is secure. We do not claim any ownership rights in the contents under your account. We may disclose the contents of your account (a) as required by law or legal process, (b) to protect or defend the rights of the Service, (c) to enforce this Agreement, or (d) to protect the interests of any other user.Prohibited BehaviorYou will not upload, store or disseminate any Content or make any Communications which violate or infringe the intellectual property or privacy rights of any person or which a reasonable person would consider abusive, profane, hateful, racially or ethnically offensive, which are defamatory or harassing, or which violate or encourage others to violate this Agreement or any applicable law. You will not upload or transmit pornographic or obscene images or files and/or information, and you will not impersonate our personnel or disrupt the orderly operation of the Service. You will not use the Service to violate any applicable law, including domestic or foreign securities laws or regulations. In order to protect itself, the Service may without liability actively cooperate with and furnish identifying and supporting information to any person likely to be harmed or affected by your violation of this Agreement and to any law enforcement agency conducting an investigation. You agree not to make any Communication that encourages users to terminate their use of the Service or to use a competitor’s service. You also agree not to make any Communication that encourages HyperOffice employees or contractors to terminate their employment or contracts with HyperOffice.You will not use our Service to make any Communications which are unsolicited bulk advertising or promotional messages (“spam”), so-called “chain letters,” pyramid schemes, or make Communications of a promotional nature other than through channels authorized by the Service. You may not harvest email addresses or instant messaging identifiers, frame the Service or its features, nor use the Service in combination with other websites or in a manner that causes confusion as to its origin.Additionally, HyperOffice reserves the right, without limitation, to terminate your access to and use of the Site and Services if, in our view, your conduct fails to meet any of the following guidelines for User conduct:You may not attempt to harm, disrupt, or otherwise engage in activity that diminishes, the HyperOffice Site, computer systems and network, or the Services.You may not attempt to interfere with any other person’s use of the Services.You may not misrepresent your identity or impersonate any person.You may not attempt to gain access to any account, computers or networks related to the Services without authorization.You may not attempt to obtain any data through any means from the Services, except if we intend to provide or make it available to you.You may not attempt to charge others to use the Services either directly or indirectly.You may not use the Services to participate in pyramid schemes or chain letters.You may not use the Services to send, either directly or indirectly, any unsolicited bulk e-mail or communications or unsolicited commercial e-mail or communications.You may not use the Services for defaming, abusing, harassing, stalking, threatening or otherwise violating the legal rights of others.You may not use the Services to send or otherwise make available, any material protected by intellectual property laws unless you own or control the rights to such material or have received all necessary consents.You may not use the Services to send or otherwise making available any material that contains viruses, Trojan horses, worms, corrupted files and/or information, or any other similar software that may damage the operation of another’s computer or property.You may not use the Services to download any material sent by another User of the Services that you know, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally distributed in such manner.You may not use the Services to violate any code of conduct or other guidelines which may be applicable to the Services or the Site.You may not use the Services to harvest or otherwise collecting information about others, including e-mail addresses.You may not attempt to modify, translate, adapt, edit, copy, decompile, disassemble, or reverse engineer any software used or provided by HyperOffice in connection with the HyperOffice Site or Services.You may not use the Services in a manner that results in excessive bandwidth usage, as determined by a representative of HyperOffice. Use of the Services on the Site as well as use of the Services on any desktop application will be applied toward such bandwidth usage.All judgments concerning the applicability of these guidelines shall be at the sole and exclusive discretion of HyperOffice.  HyperOffice reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to determine whether and what action to take in response to each such notification, and any action or inaction in a particular instance shall not dictate or limit HyperOffice’s response to a future complaint.  You acknowledge and agree that HyperOffice shall not assume or have any liability for any action or inaction by HyperOffice with respect to any User Content.  Users shall remain solely responsible for User Content, and any material or information transmitted to other Users for interaction with other Users.Software and UpdatesIf any part of our Service requires you to download a client software application (“Software”), HyperOffice hereby grants you a limited, nonexclusive, nontransferable, revocable license to use the Software, solely to access and use the Services. Your license to use the Software is automatically revoked if you violate these Terms. We hereby reserve all rights not expressly granted in these Terms. You must not reverse engineer or decompile the Software, nor attempt to do so, nor assist anyone else to do so. Our Services may update the Software on your device automatically when a new version is available.HyperOffice Property and FeedbackThese terms do not grant you any right, title, or interest in the Services or any Software used to operate the Services. While we appreciate it when users send us feedback, please be aware that we may use any feedback, comments, or suggestions you send us or post in our forums without any obligation to you. The Software and Services are protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the United States and foreign countries. HyperOffice is a service mark of the owners of this Service. These Terms do not grant you any rights to use the HyperOffice trademarks, logos, domain names, or other brand features.Other ContentThe Services may contain links to third-party websites or resources. HyperOffice does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for their availability, accuracy, the related content, products, or services. You are solely responsible for your use of any such websites or resources. If we provide you with any software under an open source license, there may be provisions in those licenses that expressly conflict with these Terms, in which case the open source provisions will apply.Force MajeureThe Service is not responsible for any delay or failure in performance of the Service in whole or in part for any reason including, without limitation: fires, floods, storms, earthquakes, civil disturbances, disruption of telecommunications, transportation, utilities, services or supplies, governmental action, computer viruses, corruption of data, hacker attack, incompatible or defective equipment, software or services or otherwise. Nothing herein enlarges any warranty or diminishes any disclaimer under this Agreement.HyperOffice is Available “AS-IS”THE SERVICES AND SOFTWARE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS”, AT YOUR OWN RISK, WITHOUT EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND. WE ALSO DISCLAIM ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. HyperOffice will have no responsibility for any harm to your computer system, loss or corruption of Content or data, or other harm that results from your access to or use of the Services or Software. Some states do not allow the types of disclaimers in this paragraph, so they may not apply to you.Limitation of LiabilityTO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL HYPEROFFICE, ITS PARENT COMPANY, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS OR LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR (A) ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL (INCLUDING LOSS OF USE, DATA, CONTENT, BUSINESS, OR PROFITS) DAMAGES, REGARDLESS OF LEGAL THEORY, WHETHER OR NOT HYPEROFFICE HAS BEEN WARNED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, AND EVEN IF A REMEDY FAILS OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE; (B) AGGREGATE LIABILITY FOR ALL CLAIMS RELATING TO THE SERVICES MORE THAN THE GREATER OF $50 OR THE AMOUNTS PAID BY YOU TO HYPEROFFICE FOR THE PAST ONE MONTH OF THE SERVICES IN QUESTION. Some states do not allow the types of limitations in this paragraph, so they may not apply to you.HyperOffice is in no way liable for loss of customer data. Under no circumstances will HyperOffice be held accountable for any loss of customer data. By becoming a HyperOffice user you, the customer, acknowledge that you forfeit the right to hold HyperOffice accountable for any and all technical errors, including loss of user files and/or information (customer data). HyperOffice intends for the information contained on its Site and Services to be accurate and reliable; however, errors sometimes may occur.  In addition, HyperOffice may make changes and improvements to the information provided herein at any time.  Application Corporation dba as HyperOffice PROVIDES ITS SITE AND SERVICES “AS IS,” “WITH ALL FAULTS” AND “AS AVAILABLE,” AND THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO SATISFACTORY QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY, AND EFFORT IS WITH YOU. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, APPLICATION CORPORATION DBA HYPEROFFICE, ITS PARENT COMPANY, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, RESELLERS, DISTRIBUTORS, SERVICE PROVIDERS AND/OR SUPPLIERS (EACH, A “HYPEROFFICE PARTY,” AND COLLECTIVELY, THE “HYPEROFFICE PARTIES”) MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED.  THE HYPEROFFICE PARTIES DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS, EXPRESS, STATUTORY AND IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION (1) WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WORKMANLIKE EFFORT, ACCURACY, TITLE, QUIET ENJOYMENT, NO ENCUMBRANCES, NO LIENS AND NON-INFRINGEMENT, (2) WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS ARISING THROUGH COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE, AND (3) WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS THAT ACCESS TO OR USE OF THE WEB SITES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE.  SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS, SO SOME OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.  THERE ARE NO WARRANTIES THAT EXTEND BEYOND THE FACE OF THIS CONTRACT.IndemnificationYou agree to defend, indemnify and hold the Service harmless from any damage, liability, cost or expense (including legal fees of the Service) arising from any third party claim proximately caused by your violation of these Terms, provided you are given the right to control the defense of such claim and any settlement that does not adversely affect the Service.Protected PartiesTHE WARRANTY DISCLAIMERS, LIABILITY LIMITS, INDEMNITIES AND RESERVATION OF RIGHTS CONTAINED IN THIS AGREEMENT PROTECT THE SERVICE, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, OWNERS, AGENTS, PROGRAMMERS, CONSULTANTS, ATTORNEYS AND ADVISERS, EMPLOYEES, AFFILIATES, ADVERTISERS, DISTRIBUTORS, RESELLERS, SUPPLIERS, PUBLISHERS AND PROMOTERS.ModificationsWe may revise these Terms from time to time and the most current version will always be posted on our website. By continuing to access or use the Services after revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please stop using the Services.REFUNDSUnder no circumstances shall you be eligible to receive reimbursement, in whole or in part, of any payment to HyperOffice unless the Products and Services were unable to be used as a result of uptime of the Products and Services below 99.9% for a certain thirty (30) day payment period. In this limited event, you shall be eligible to receive a pro rata (1/30th of the payment due on the payment date immediately subsequent to the date during which the Products and Services were unable to be used) reimbursement for each individual day during the thirty (30) day payment period for which the uptime of the Products and Services was below 99.9%. To qualify for a pro rata reimbursement of payment under this Section, you must notify HyperOffice in writing within seventy-two (72) hours of such inability to use Products and Services. HyperOffice, in its sole discretion, shall determine whether uptime of the Products and Services was below 99.9% for a certain thirty (30) day payment period.TERMINATION AND CANCELLATIONUnless superseded by another agreement with HyperOffice, HyperOffice may immediately terminate, at any time and without notice and without penalty, your limited, non-exclusive, and non-transferable right to use the Products and Services upon your breach of any provision of these Terms of Use.Your cancellation of any agreement, whereby you have the right to use the Products and Services, including your obligation to make timely payment of any amount owed for the right to use the Products and Services and to adhere to these Terms of Use, shall not be effective until you complete the following cancellation process:Make a cancellation request in writing on the company letterhead and signed by an authorized company executive at least 30 days before the requested cancellation date.Send this request via email to spbilling@hyperoffice.com or toApplication Corporation, d/b/a HyperOfficePO BOX 10341Rockville, Maryland 20849USANo method, other than completion of the cancellation process described above shall be effective to discontinue your obligation to make timely payment of any amount owed for the right to use the Products and Services and to adhere to these Terms of Use. Unless and until you have cancelled your account, you agree that HyperOffice may automatically invoice or charge the credit card on file for the full amount of each succeeding month’s subscription, or in the case of an annual subscription, for each succeeding year. If either HyperOffice terminates, or you cancel, your right to use the Products and Services, HyperOffice shall have all the legally available rights and privileges to receive any outstanding amount owed by you to HyperOffice. In addition, if you are a party to a Reseller Agreement, HyperOffice shall have all the legally available rights and privileges to receive directly from you any outstanding amount owed by you to Reseller for your right to use the Products and Services if (i) payment for your right to use the Products and Services has not been made by you to Reseller; and (ii) Reseller has not effectuated payment for your right to use the Products and Services to HyperOffice.Choice of Law and ForumTHESE TERMS AND THE USE OF THE SERVICES AND SOFTWARE WILL BE GOVERNED BY MARYLAND LAW EXCEPT FOR ITS CONFLICTS OF LAWS PRINCIPLES. ALL CLAIMS ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS OR THE SERVICES OR SOFTWARE MUST BE LITIGATED EXCLUSIVELY IN THE FEDERAL OR STATE COURTS OF MONTGOMERY COUNTY, MARYLAND (USA), AND BOTH PARTIES IRREVOCABLY CONSENT TO VENUE AND PERSONAL JURISDICTION THEREIN.These Terms of Use shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Maryland, excluding its conflicts-of-law principles. Please note that your use of the Services may be subject to other local, state, national, and international laws. You expressly agree that exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or dispute with HyperOffice or relating in any way to your use of the Services resides in the courts of Maryland and you further agree and expressly consent to the exercise of personal jurisdiction in the courts of Maryland in connection with any such dispute including any claim involving HyperOffice or its affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, contractors, officers, directors, telecommunication providers and content providers.EUROPEAN USERSBy using the HyperOffice product and services, users in the European Union understand and consent to the processing of personal information in the United States.Injunctive ReliefIf you violate or exceed the scope of these Terms or infringe our proprietary rights, you agree we would be irreparably harmed and may (in addition to other relief and without having to post bond or proving actual damage) obtain a court order obtaining specific performance or enjoining you from further mischief. You agree to pay our reasonable legal fees in any action to enforce these rights in which we substantially prevail.Relationship of the Parties  There are no third party beneficiaries of this Agreement. The parties are independent to one another and are not related by franchise, partnership, employment, joint venture or otherwise. This Service is not a party to any transaction between you and any third party advertisers or suppliers. You will look solely to the third party for all claims regarding their goods, services or information.GeneralThese Terms constitute the entire and exclusive agreement between you and HyperOffice with respect to the Services and any Software, and supersede and replace any other agreements, terms and conditions applicable to this subject matter. HyperOffice’s failure to enforce a provision is not a waiver of its right to do so later. If a provision is found unenforceable the remaining provisions of the Agreement will remain in full effect and the unenforceable term shall be deemed revised to reflect our intent as closely as possible. You may not assign any of your rights in these Terms, and any such attempt is void, but HyperOffice may assign its rights to any of its affiliates or subsidiaries, or to any successor in interest of any business associated with the Services. The parties agree that electronic mail and other electronic communications and notices posted on the Service or transmitted between them shall be effective written communications, unless other specific notice provisions are provided herein.MISCELLANEOUS.HyperOffice may assign this contract, in whole or in part, at any time with or without notice to you. You may not assign this contract, or any part of it, to any other party. Any attempt by you to do so is void.  ANY CLAIM RELATED TO THIS CONTRACT OR THE SOFTWARE AND SERVICE MUST BE BROUGHT WITHIN ONE YEAR.  THE ONE-YEAR PERIOD BEGINS ON THE DATE WHEN THE CLAIM FIRST COULD BE FILED. IF IT IS NOT, THEN THAT CLAIM IS PERMANENTLY BARRED. THIS APPLIES TO YOU AND YOUR SUCCESSORS.  IT ALSO APPLIES TO US AND OUR SUCCESSORS AND ASSIGNS.  The failure of HyperOffice to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the terms and conditions shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. The section titles in these terms and conditions are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect.COPYRIGHT COMPLAINTS AND REMOVAL POLICYHyperOffice provides services that permit registered users of the HyperOffice services (“Users”) to store content on the Web. HyperOffice does not tolerate infringing material on its equipment or network, and may remove content that appears to infringe any copyright or other intellectual property rights or otherwise violates HyperOffice Terms of Use, found on the HyperOffice Web site (http://www.HyperOffice.com).If you believe that your copyright in any material has been infringed on a site hosted on HyperOffice’s equipment or through its services, please send a DMCA Notice, (described below) to HyperOffice’s Copyright Agent for Notice of Claims of Copyright Infringement. Once we receive a complete DMCA Notice, we will then evaluate your notice and take such action as is appropriate under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (.DMCA.), 17 U.S.C. § 512 et seq.Federal law requires your DMCA Notice to include the following information:Identification of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;Identification of the material, including URL, that you claim is infringing, with enough detail so that we may locate it;Your address, telephone number, and e-mail address;A statement declaring under penalty of perjury that (a) you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; (b) the above information in your notice is accurate, and (c) you are the owner of the copyright interest involved or you are authorized to act on behalf of that owner; andYour physical or electronic signature.HyperOffice’s Copyright Agent for Notice of Claims of Copyright Infringement can be reached as follows:Attn: DMCA Copyright AgentApplication Corporation, d/b/a HyperOfficePO BOX 10341Rockville, Maryland 20849USAPlease note that HyperOffice, in its sole discretion, may terminate the account of any User about whom HyperOffice receives more than one complaint of copyright infringement.If you have any questions about this policy, please contact legal@hyperoffice.comNotice of Copyright Infringement ProceduresIf you believe content on our Service infringes your copyrighted work and you want the Service to take down the offending material, you will need to complete the following Notice of Copyright Infringement and mail or fax it to our Registered Agent (do not use this procedure for any other kind of communication):Mail us:Customer Relations DepartmentApplication Corporation d/b/a HyperOfficeEmail it to: legal@hyperoffice.comApplication Corporation, d/b/a HyperOfficePO BOX 10341Rockville, Maryland 20849USANotice of Copyright Infringement (Please complete):I certify under the penalty of perjury that I own or am authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyrighted work identified below. I believe in good faith that the copyrighted work has been used on your Service without authorization by the owner, its agents or according to law. I ask that you remove or block access to the infringing material.Name of Copyright Owner:Description of Copyrighted Work:Description of Infringing Material:Location of Infringing Material:I can be contacted as follows:My Name:My Title:Company:Address:Address:Telephone:Fax:Email:I certify under the penalties of perjury that the foregoing is true and correct to the best of my information, knowledge and belief.Signed:Date:INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS AND NOTICES.Except for the licenses granted herein, you have no right, title or interest in or to HyperOffice Services or any content. You agree that HyperOffice or its licensors retain all proprietary right, title and interest, including copyright and all other intellectual property rights, in and to HyperOffice service and content, including, without limitation, text, images, and other multimedia data.All contents of the HyperOffice’s Site and Services including but not limited to design, text, software, technical drawings, configurations, graphics, other files and/or information, and their selection and arrangement (“Content”) are: Copyright © 2011 HyperOffice, and/or the proprietary property of its suppliers, affiliates, or licensors.  Content may not be reproduced, modified, derivative works created from, displayed, performed, published, distributed, disseminated, broadcasted or circulated to any third party (including, without limitation, the display and distribution of the material via a third party Web site or other networked computer environment) without the express prior written consent of HyperOffice and/or it suppliers, affiliates, or licensors.  All rights reserved.HyperOffice, the HyperOffice logo, HyperBase, ushare.to, and share.to are including without limitation, either trademarks, service marks or registered trademarks of HyperOffice, and may not be copied, imitated, or used, in whole or in part, without HyperOffice’s prior written permission or that of our suppliers or licensors.  Other product and company names may be trade or service marks of their respective owners.HyperOffice may have patents, patent applications, trademarks, copyrights, or other intellectual property rights covering subject matter in its Site that are part of the Services.  Unless we have granted you licenses to our intellectual property in these terms and conditions, our providing you with such Web pages does not give you any license to our intellectual property.  Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.HyperOffice Privacy PolicyLast Modified: December, 2019Your privacy is important to Application Corporation dba as HyperOffice (hereinafter referred to as, “HyperOffice”). This privacy policy (“Policy”) applies to the HyperOffice web services and tells you how personal information is collected, used, disclosed, and protected by HyperOffice.This Privacy Policy provides our policies and procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information. Users can access the HyperOffice service (the “Service”) through the internet, applications on Devices, through APIs, and through third-parties. A “Device” is any computer used to access the HyperOffice Service, including without limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other consumer electronic device. This Privacy Policy governs your access of the HyperOffice Service, regardless of how you access it, and by using our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy. All of the different forms of data, content, and information described below are collectively referred to as “information.”1. The Information We Collect And StoreWe may collect and store the following information when running the HyperOffice Service:Information You Provide.   When you register an account, we collect some personal information, such as your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses. You may also ask us to import your contacts by giving us access to your third party services (for example, your email account) or to use your social networking information if you give us access to your account on social network connection services. You may also provide us with your contacts’ email addresses when sharing folders or files with them.Files.   We collect and store the files you upload, download, or access with the HyperOffice Service (“Files”). If you add a file to your HyperOffice that has been previously uploaded by you or another user, we may associate all or a portion of the previous file with your account rather than storing a duplicate.Log Data.   When you use the Service, we automatically record information from your Device, its software, and your activity using the Services. This may include the Device’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, the web page visited before you came to our website, information you search for on our website, locale preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, date and time stamps associated with transactions, system configuration information, metadata concerning your Files, and other interactions with the Service.2. How We Use Personal InformationPersonal Information:   In the course of using the Service, we may collect personal information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is or may be used: (i) to provide and improve our Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service, (iii) to better understand your needs and interests, (iv) to personalize and improve your experience, and (v) to provide or offer software updates and product announcements. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of those communications, or update your account settings information.3. Information Sharing and DisclosureYour Use.   We will display your Personal Information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Service according to the preferences you set in your account. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want others to know about you. Please consider carefully what information you disclose in your profile page and your desired level of anonymity. You can review and revise your profile information at any time. We may also share or disclose your information with your consent, for example if you use a third party application to access your account (see below). Through certain features of the Service, you may also have the ability to make some of your information public. Public information may be broadly and quickly disseminated.Service Providers, Business Partners and Others.   We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service’s features). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy.Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of HyperOffice’s Rights.   We may disclose to parties outside HyperOffice information stored in your HyperOffice and information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of HyperOffice or its users; or (d) to protect HyperOffice’s property rights. If we provide your HyperOffice files to a law enforcement agency as set forth above, we will remove HyperOffice’s encryption from the files before providing them to law enforcement. However, HyperOffice will not be able to decrypt any files that you encrypted prior to storing them on HyperOffice.Business Transfers.   If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your Personal Information or shared information, or if either become subject to a different Privacy Policy. We will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information.Non-private or Non-Personal Information.   We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our Service.4. Changing or Deleting Your InformationIf you are a registered user, you may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information provided in your registration or account profile by changing your “account settings.” If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete it by making the change on your account settings. In some cases we may retain copies of your information if required by law.5. Data RetentionWe will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, you may delete your account by contacting support@hyperoffice.com . We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your information quickly upon request. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion. In addition, we do not delete from our servers files that you have in common with other users.6. HyperOffice CommunityOur Service offers publicly accessible community services such as blogs, forums, and wikis. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. Your posts may remain even after you cancel your account.7. SecurityThe security of your information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).We follow generally accepted standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at info@hyperoffice.com.8. GDPR at HyperOffice Privacy and security have always been the foundation of our approach to product development and business, and we continuously evaluate all our practices in an effort to safeguard your information as effectively as possible. In that vein, we’re glad to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and to help our customers comply with the GDPR.What is GDPR?On May 25, 2018, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) will officially take effect. For European individuals, the GDPR expands their data privacy rights and gives them more power to control their data. For companies that process the personal data of these European individuals, the GDPR requires compliance with a new set of regulations.The GDPR outlines specific requirements that these companies must satisfy, as well as specific rights that European individuals can exercise with these companies. Further information on the GDPR is available on the European Union’s official website: https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection_en.Controllers and ProcessorsThe GDPR defines and distinguishes between two types of parties and responsibilities when it comes to collecting and processing personal data: data controllers and data processors. A data controller determines the purposes and ways that personal data is processed, while a data processor is a party that process data on behalf of the controller. That means that the controller could be any company or organization. A processor could be a SaaS, IT or other company that is actually processing the data on behalf of the controller. Hyperoffice is a Data Processor. HyperOffice customers (the organizations who use HyperOffice) are Data Controllers. The controller is responsible to make sure that all processors with whom it deals will be GDPR compliant and the processors themselves must keep records of their processing activities.Data processing agreementHyperOffice offers Data Processing Agreements (DPAs) to users upon request. This DPA includes standard contractual clauses (“Model Clauses”) that are the mechanism for GDPR-compliant data transfer. To request a DPA, please email privacy@hyperoffice.com from the email address associated with your Airtable account.Features to support GDPR requirementsHyperOffice can help you meet your data portability requirements for the GDPR. You can easily export data and permanently delete data from WorkMap.ai and certain modules in Atlas, and ushare.to.Data Protection OfficerWe have appointed a Data Protection Officer. For more information, contact privacy@hyperoffice.com9. Our Policy Toward ChildrenOur Services are not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at support@hyperoffice.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will take steps to delete such information from our files.10. Contacting UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@HyperOffice.com.11. Changes to our Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make a change to this privacy policy that we believe materially reduces your rights, we will provide you with notice (for example, by email). And we may provide notice of changes in other circumstances as well. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.12. Enforcement/Dispute ResolutionTo file a complaint regarding this Policy, you should contact HyperOffice at legal@HyperOffice.com. HyperOffice’s General Counsel will explain the process to be followed when filing a complaint and will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information by referencing the privacy principles stated in this Policy.13. Publicly AvailableHyperOffice will work with you to resolve any concerns you may have about this Policy. To ask questions regarding this Policy or any of HyperOffices’s privacy practices, request the deletion of personal information, or issue a complaint, you can contact HyperOffice via email privacy@hyperoffice.com – or mail at the following address:HyperOfficePO BOX 10341Rockville, Maryland 20849USAA copy of our privacy policy is also available athttps://www.hyperoffice.com/terms-of-use/This website, www.hyperoffice.com (the “Website”), is operated by HyperOffice.What are cookies?Cookies are a small text files that are stored in your web browser that allows HyperOffice or a third party to recognize you. Cookies can be used to collect, store and share bits of information about your activities across websites, including on HyperOffice website.Cookies might be used for the following purposes:To enable certain functionsTo provide analyticsTo store your preferencesTo enable ad delivery and behavioral advertisingHyperOffice uses both session cookies and persistent cookies.A session cookie is used to identify a particular visit to our Website. These cookies expire after a short time, or when you close your web browser after using our Website. We use these cookies to identify you during a single browsing session, such as when you log into our Website.A persistent cookie will remain on your devices for a set period of time specified in the cookie. We use these cookies where we need to identify you over a longer period of time. For example, we would use a persistent cookie if you asked that we keep you signed in.How do third parties use cookies on the HyperOffice Website?Third party companies like analytics companies and ad networks generally use cookies to collect user information on an anonymous basis. They may use that information to build a profile of your activities on the HyperOffice Website and other websites that you’ve visited.What are your cookies options?If you don’t like the idea of cookies or certain types of cookies, you can change your browser’s settings to delete cookies that have already been set and to not accept new cookies. To learn more about how to do this, visit the help pages of your browser.Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or do not accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.CompanyAbout usContact usIn the newsPress releasesCareersTerms of useService providersResourcesSitemapCommunityBlogTwitterFacebookLinkedinYoutubeProducts and ServicesAtlas Collaboration SuiteOther productsProfessional servicesSupportLanguagesEnglishSpanish Founded in 1998, HyperOffice is a market leader in cloud collaboration and communication software for small and medium sized businesses. We provide the most comprehensive suite of solutions developed over more than 12 years of understanding your growing business needs. HyperOffice's capabilities include customer portal & intranet software, online document management, online project management, shared calendars, contact management software, online database software and web forms, team communication, and much more - offered as an integrated, easy to use solution accessible over any web connected PC, Mac, or mobile device. HyperOffice is also a viable Microsoft Sharepoint alternative for collaboration, and Microsoft Access alternative for online access to databases. Hyperoffice empowers growing companies looking for the power of enterprise class messaging and collaboration - but without the associated costs and hassles.© 2020 HyperOffice.
ProductsWorkMap.ai Workflows/Databases (formerly HyperBase)Atlas Intranet SuiteuShare.to Team Communicationhims.ai Healthcare Admin. AutomationSolutionsWorkflow AutomationOnline Relational DatabasesAccess Database OnlineOnline Database ManagementMicrosoft Access AlternativeReplace Excel & Google SheetsSocial IntranetSharePoint AlternativeCustomer PortalOnline Document ManagementMorePricingIndustriesIndustry SolutionsIndustry Case StudiesFree Trial WorkMap.ai Online Databases & Workflows (formerly HyperBase)uShare.to Team Communication Atlas Intranet Suite Talk to an expert
We use cookies on this website. By continuing, you agree to our cookie policy. OkCookie Policy
